[Episode 11]
Mister.
I'll save him.
I'll save Yun.
Mister.
So don't cry.
I can't stand watching you cry.
You look as ugly as Shrek when you cry.
I'll give my heart to Yun, okay?
Mister.
I'll give my heart to Yun,
so will you be with me?
Will you just stay with me while I'm still alive?
Did you think about it?
What's there to think about? Let's do that. Okay?
It's good for you, me, Yun, and Yun's mom.
It's a fantastic idea in my opinion.
Bastard...
You know how to cuss, Blockhead?
You bastard...
Fine, take it out! Give your heart to him!
Take it out!
Not now. I'll do it later.
I want to have good times with you and have fun.
Don't I get anything in return?
I'll give it to him later.
How can you stoop that low?
Death is not a joke.
Go to hell, you bastard.
Are you okay?
Hey! Hey, are you okay?
Go away...
Hey, are you okay?
Get your hands off me!
I'll give my heart to Yun,
so will you be with me?
Will you just stay with me while I'm still alive?
Just save Yun. Save him.
Yun, my Yun! If you could just save my Yun!
What did I do to deserve this?
What did I do wrong?
I've donated three or four times more than others...
I'm even anonymously helping 12 families!
But he's always cruel to me... Always!
Do you want to go all the way?
Do you really want to see how cruel
you can be to me?
Ma'am!
Didn't you hear me before?
Didn't you hear from Mr. Kang to hire a new manager?
Please go inside, ma'am.
Why are you ignoring me?
Do you think what I say is a joke?
Mr. Cha is doing a good job.
He's sincere, reliable, and smart...
I get so furious just looking at him.
If he had been there for Yun,
none of this would've ever happened.
Stop being stubborn and let's go inside.
Why are you keep blaming Mr. Cha?
I didn't like him from the beginning. I didn't.
I really didn't like him at all.
Open the door.
Find a replacement immediately.
Seeing his face over and over is just torturous.
I can't take it.
Eunchae.
Eunchae!
Ma'am!
Eunchae.
I'm so thankful to you, Eunchae.
Come here.
I'll fix up Yun for sure, Eunchae. Whatever it takes.
I'll make sure Yun will be healthy again, Eunchae.
So don't go anywhere and stay next to my Yun.
I'm so sorry, but please stay beside
my Yun, okay?
Mr. Cha.
Don't get mad over what Yun's mom said.
It's because she's gotten more sensitive.
Yes.
And... Start looking for some other job.
I'm sorry she blamed you,
but it's better for you and Yun's mom
if you give up the job now.
I'm sorry.
I'll ask Mr. Kang to be generous
with your final paycheck.
Is your sister doing well?
Yes.
I'll stay here. You should go home and get some rest.
You should have gone with your dad earlier.
I can stay here.
I'm worried that you'll get sick because of Yun.
Look at your face. It's gotten all rough.
But Yun will be looking for me.
I'll take care of it. Just go home.
- Okay, I'll go home then. Take care.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
Your fare.
- Don't you have any smaller bill?
- No, keep the change.
[I'm not kidding]
I'm not kidding.
Why would I joke about death?
Maximum three months. Minimum...
How long would that be?
Should have asked the doctor that.
I'll be dead around then.
If I do one good thing before I die,
maybe I won't go to hell.
And it will be good for you, Yun, and Yun's mom.
Don't you think it's a good deal?
I've even checked with the doctor.
My heart is perfect for Yun's transplant, luckily.
Wait for me, Blockhead!
Blockhead!
If you don't want me to. I will never touch you.
Not even your hair.
Okay, that's a lie.
I might still kiss you.
But if you really don't want to,
then I won't do that, either.
I'll just look at you.
Not hold your hand and not kiss you.
Come be with me. Come be with me, Blockhead.
I didn't hear you before.
Can you tell me again?
When are you dying, Mister?
Maximum three months. Minimum...
Didn't ask.
You're definitely going to die, right, Mister?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll be with you.
I'd do anything to save Yun.
With every fiber of my being.
I'd even sleep with you.
Just make sure you really die.
Die for sure and save Yun. Keep your promise.
[Unlucky star Audrey]
[Written by the twins she abandoned:
Cha Muhyeok and Yun Seo-kyeong]
Who are you?
Death is not a joke.
Go to hell, you bastard.
I want to take Muhyeok's hand.
You don't need me.
You've always been fine without me.
You'll be fine without me.
So when a thug grabs you like this...
And says, "Hey, wanna mess around with me?"
Then twist his wrist like this,
and kick him where it hurts!
Then even the biggest guy
wouldn't be able to do anything.
Try it.
Twist it like this? Like this?
Not like that.
Twist with all your strength,
as if your life depends on it.
I don't wanna do it. I can't do it.
What if the thugs come again?
Are you gonna let them do whatever?
You can beat them up.
Thugs around here are so afraid of you...
I started a rumor
that you are a very scary thug yourself.
Yeah, Uncle is the scariest thug of all.
Right, Galchi?
Don't worry... As long as you're around...
They won't touch my mom. Don't worry.
Don't worry.
What if I'm not around?
What are you going to do if I'm not around?
You said you wouldn't go to Australia.
You said you will live with us for a long, long time.
How can I live with you for a long, long time?
I have my own life to live.
You should work out.
You have to protect your mom when I'm not around.
Let's do it again. What did I tell you to do?
What are you doing? Show me what you would do!
Do it.
Geez.
Are you going to die for sure, Mister?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll be with you.
I'd do anything to save Yun.
With every fiber of my being.
I'd even sleep with you.
Just make sure you really die.
Die for sure and save Yun. Keep your promise.
This is Ogalpi tea with shiitake mushroom honey.
I heard it was good for the heart,
so stayed up all night making it.
Give it to Yun.
Thank you, Mom.
But Eunchae...
I'm not sure if it's okay to keep
sending you to Yun like this.
Why not?
Well... What if Yun suddenly dies?
- Mom!
Celebrity gossip is crazy.
And you're not even Yun's wife.
What if bad rumors start?
Then no one will want to marry you.
- Mom!
I'll bring it to him now.
Oh, okay.
Be careful.
Trying having your own kids, brats!
Stop staring!
How dare you stare at your mother like that!
Maybe you're right.
Look at Yun's mom.
She looked down on Eunchae when Yun was doing well.
And now that she needs her...
She's like, "Eunchae! Eunchae!"
"Eunchae!"
Is Eunchae the community service leader
in this town or something?
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, right.
You two were more interested in
making Yun a part of the family!
"I can't wait to tell them that
Choi Yun will be my son-in-law!
Everyone will die from jealousy!"
When did I say that?
"Choi Yun will be my brother-in-law!
They will all be so jealous!"
I said that? When?
You two are so fair-weathered.
You switch sides on a whim.
I'm starting to feel disillusioned, really.
- I know.
I'm outside to get some fresh air.
Yeah. Yun is asleep.
I've sent some Ogalpi tea and
mushroom honey with Eunchae.
Give it to him regularly, even if he doesn't like it.
Thank you. How can I repay you?
You don't owe me anything. We are friends.
When Yun gets healthy let's become in-laws!
Okay. Future in-law.
I think Eunchae's car is pulling in.
Yeah, future in-law.
Wait, Yun is calling.
I'll call you later, okay?
Yun. Are you awake, son?
Yeah, it's Mom. I'm coming inside.
Blockhead.
Let's date.
You said you would do anything. Did you forget already?
Should we take my car or your car?
Eunchae's Mom had Eunchae bring
Ogalpi tea and honey for you.
Is Eunchae coming right now?
Yeah I saw her parking the car.
She should be coming in.
I talked to Eunchae's mom about
you and Eunchae getting married.
Huh?
We agree that it's a good idea.
So get well soon, okay?
Are you that happy?
Don't laugh. You'll just strain yourself!
Don't laugh.
Afraid?
Scared, right?
Let me know if you're not up to it.
We can always call off the promise.
You wish I would say that, right?
I don't don't do take-backs.
I don't have that kind of time.
- Are you on drugs?
- Yep.
- Did you get shot in the head?
How did you know that?
Fine. Do as you wish, Mister.
I wanted to give my own heart to Yun,
but since you want to volunteer, I'm thankful.
How can I ever repay you for this?
Tell me if you want anything. I'll give you anything.
Just tell me. I'll give you the works.
It was Eunchae and Eunchae's car for sure.
Try calling her cell.
Mom.
Yes, son?
Am I too selfish?
Huh?
Eunchae doesn't even want to...
Am I giving Eunchae a hard time because I'm greedy?
Eunchae was secretly in love with you
for over 20 years.
Eunchae's family thinks it's something glorious.
That's all in the past.
Didn't you say you wanted to get her no matter what?
I thought you couldn't live without Eunchae.
Don't overcomplicate it.
Do whatever it takes to get her, no matter what.
I'm not sure.
I'm suddenly not sure about anything, Mom.
Don't frown.
I told you that you look so ugly when you cry that
I can't handle it, didn't I?
You're not playing fair. Song Eunchae!
Don't think about him while you're with me.
Don't think about anything while you're with me.
Don't cry. Don't even frown.
Don't be sad or tormented.
Don't say you want to go home. Don't worry about Yun.
Don't let any of those feelings show.
Mister!
I've put my heart on the line to be with you.
Focus on me.
Recipient is not available. Forwarding to voicemail...
[Yun]
Yes, sir.
Yes. I'm okay. Thank you for your concern.
By the way, could you tell me Muhyeok's home address?
The bullet is embedded between the blood vessels,
adding more and more pressure
to your brain as time passes.
Is death really my only option?
Tell me if you want anything. I'll give you anything.
Just tell me. I'll give you the works.
Is that what you wanted?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Okay, follow me, Mister.
Blockhead, what are you doing right now?
Are you really going to do "anything"?
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
You thought right.
I'd do "anything" for Yun. No matter what it is.
Good thinking, Mister.
I can even die for Yun.
I wouldn't regret it for a moment.
Die for sure, Mister.
For Yun, die for sure, Mister! For Yun...
I told you not to talk about Yun!
Yun will...
I said don't talk about him!
Yun will understand.
I'll tell him I had to do it to save him.
Because I made a deal. That I had no choice.
Yun will understand.
Get your filthy hands off me!
I'll undress myself.
Thank you, Mister.
For saving Yun.
I'll never forget your kindness as long as I live.
Yun?
Son?
The Rose of Sharon is in bloom.
Hello. Do you remember me?
Who are you?
Choi Yun!
You're Choi Yun the singer, right?
I'm sorry for what happened last time.
My mom found the ring.
I'll apologize on her behalf.
Is Muhyeok home?
- Galchi?
- Yes.
[To Galchi: Choi Yun]
There you go.
I heard you're really sick.
I'm okay.
When is your uncle coming home?
I don't know. Call his cell.
He's not answering his cell.
Excuse me... Sign one for me, too, like Galchi's.
Sure. Bring me some paper.
I'm gonna ask him to do it on
the biggest sheet of paper.
[Muhyeok / Yun Seo-kyeong / Galchi]
[Uncle / Eunchae]
[Hospital Record - Cha Muhyeok]
Whose is this?
It's Uncle's.
It's just a pirate. Give me an autograph! Sign it!
You said you'd give me an autograph!
Sign it for me!
[8 missed calls from Mom]
[My Eunchae]
Recipient is not available. Forwarding to voicemail...
[Muhyeok]
So did he report her missing?
Yeah. Dad called it in around seven this morning.
You don't think she was kidnapped, do you?
Don't say such scary things.
Aren't you late for school?
How can you worry about school right now?
I need to go look for Eunchae.
How? Her cell doesn't even work.
What if something happened to Eunchae?
I wasn't even a good sister to her.
What about me? I wasn't good to her at all either.
Eunchae?
Eunchae...
Eunchae... Eunchae...
Where were you? We were so worried.
Were you with Eunchae?
Do you know that Yun and Eunchae's
families were freaking out all night?
Now you're going to seduce Eunchae?
Are you going to take everything away from Yun?
How much do you want to ruin Yun?
Yun doesn't have anything to lose anymore.
I don't know what kind of grudge
you have against him but...
Stop it now, please.
Yun only has Eunchae left...
Let the two of them be.
I'll tell Eunchae!
That you deliberately approached her to ruin Yun.
Just like you did to me. That you're only using her.
I'll tell her.
Hey, get up, Song Eunchae.
Get up, Song Eunchae!
Where did you go and what were you doing, you brat?
This brat is out to kill me from stress!
Tell me. What were you doing with whom with
your phone off and coming home so late?
Why didn't you answer your phone? Why didn't you call?
Let's leave.
I don't think she slept. Let her sleep. Let's go.
She's not sleeping.
She's just acting because she can't even make excuses.
Song Eunchae! Answer me!
Are you ignoring your mother right now?
Quiet! Just let her sleep!
Let me go. What are you doing?
Let's leave!
You shouldn't do that. You shouldn't do that to Yun!
Yun almost died while looking for you
in his condition, you awful brat! You're a witch!
Be quiet!
She changed her mind because Yun is not well.
I can't believe how much she's changed!
Just be quiet!
There are no critical problems.
It can get worse at any time,
so rest well and be careful.
Yes, doctor.
Thank you, doctor.
How is Yun doing?
Mr. Song.
Is Eunchae back?
Yes.
Where did she say she was?
I didn't ask. She's sleeping right now.
When Eunchae wakes up, tell her I want to see her.
I didn't know Eunchae could do such a thing.
I didn't think Eunchae would stab
us in the back like this.
Eunchae should at least...
Mom... Can you wait outside?
Yeah?
I have something to talk about with Mr. Song.
About what?
All right.
Is Eunchae doing fine?
Yes.
Don't scold Eunchae too much.
She was probably with Muhyeok last night.
I understand.
Mr. Song.
Okay.
No. Lay back down.
What is this?
Enclosed is the name of the hospital and doctor.
Will you see what this is about?
I was told they belong to Muhyeok.
Yes, they're x-rays of Mr. Cha Muhyeok.
I was shocked at first as well.
I thought this kind of thing only happened on TV.
I didn't think I'd ever see this
sort of thing with my own eyes.
It's a miracle that he's even alive.
I can't explain it any other way.
Did... Did he tell you how it happened?
He was shot twice at his ex-girlfriend's wedding.
Fortunately, one bullet was surgically removed,
but the other couldn't be removed
because it was too dangerous.
So... What happens now?
I don't think there will be a second miracle.
He's dying.
Mr. Cha Muhyeok is dying. There's no hope for him.
Where is my baby? Mr. Song! Where is my baby?
You know, right?
Where is my baby?
Where did you hide my baby?
The baby died.
Lies! That's a lie! That can't be.
Why? Why would the baby die?
Where is he?
Bring my baby here right now, Mom.
How would I bring it back from the dead?
Daecheon threw the ashes into a river yesterday.
Forget it!
At the time, she was a famous actress
and the father was a married man. A movie director.
Hey, do you wanna have a good time?
Those children shouldn't have been born.
The two children were mere obstacles
in the way of Audrey's bright future.
Uncle! I'm dizzy!
Are you sure? Are you sure that's what he said?
Are you sure he didn't confuse
Muhyeok with someone else?
Eunchae.
You're going to catch a cold.
Let's go in, okay?
I"m fine.
The doctor said it was okay to take a walk for a bit.
I feel good today.
Sorry.
Sorry about yesterday, Yun.
Were you with Muhyeok?
I won't do it again.
It won't happen again.
Yeah. Don't do it again.
Don't see Muhyeok anymore.
I'm not going to die, Song Eunchae!
If I were to die after I asked you to be with me,
what would become of you?
I'm not that selfish.
I'm going to live.
I'll recover no matter what.
I can do it!
I'll live for you.
Even if it kills me, I'll live.
Okay, Yun. Okay.
Who is it? Who is it?
This is Jang Taeseok from TV Celeb Journal.
So?
Just wanted to show your love to our audience.
Forgive me.
Even celebrities are entitled to
have a private life, don't you think?
If you don't like it, I'll destroy the tape.
Please think about it and
give me permission to release it.
Eat up.
What are you guys doing?
Kissing up.
- What?
- We're kissing up to you.
Did you two do something wrong?
Seo-kyeong, did you wet your pants again?
No. No, we didn't.
We're kissing up so you don't go back to Australia.
We're kissing up to you so you'll live with us.
Live with us, Uncle!
I really won't make you mad anymore.
Fine. I'll see how well you guys do.
Then, I'll decide whether or not I go back.
Oh! It's Eunchae! Eunchae!
It's Eunchae!
It's Yun!
I got his autograph.
[Their unwavering love is setting an example for many]
Oh! Eunchae!
It's Eunchae!
I'll tell him I had to do it to save him.
Because I made a deal. That I had no choice.
Yun will understand.
[Episode 12 Preview]
Should I just forgive her?
That pretty lady.
Should we forgive her?
[Sorry, I too want to forgive]
What can you do for Eunchae?
If it were me, if I thought I couldn't do
anything for the girl I loved,
I would give her up.
[Love, disappear from my life now]
Don't come here again. Get lost, Mister.
Please get out of my life.